const questions = [
    {
        prompt: "Who was Cristiano Ronaldo dos Santos Aveiro named after?",
        answers: ["Ronaldo Nazario (R9)", "US President Ronald Reagan", "Ron Jimmons (WWE Wrestler)", "His singer sister Liliana Catia's stage name Ronalda"],
        correctAnswer: "US President Ronald Reagan",
        explanation: "He was born just a month after the actor-turned-politician Reagan had been sworn in for his second term in the White House. It is believed his mother was a fan of the 40th US president."
    },
    {
        prompt: "What was the most serious health condition/injury Ronaldo faced in his life?",
        answers: ["Tachycardia Disease", "Patellar Tendonitis (2014)", "Knee Injury (2016 EURO Final)", "Covid-19"],
        correctAnswer: "Tachycardia Disease",
        explanation: "Cristiano Ronaldo was diagnosed with Tachycardia, a term for a rapid heartbeat of over 100 times per minute. This can lead to stroke or heart failure so, at the age of 15, he underwent heart surgery. Mind-blowing huh, there would be no CR7 if it wasn't for that doctor."
    },
    {
        prompt: "How many goals did CR7 score throughout his career?",
        answers: ["777 goals", "856 goals", "873 goals", "899 goals"],
        correctAnswer: "873 goals",
        explanation: "Cristiano Ronaldo is the highest goalscorer in the world, with 873 goals scored in all competitions. CR7 is currently 52 goals ahead of his biggest rival Lionel Messi (821)."
    },
    {
        prompt: "How many cars does CR7 have?",
        answers: ["2", "5", "10", "20"],
        correctAnswer: "20",
        explanation: "Like many of his peers, Ronaldo loves cars and owns as many as 20 luxurious cars, the most famous ones being a Bugatti Chiron, Ferrari 599 GTO and Rolls-Royce Phantom."
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which University has a sociology course about Cristiano Ronaldo?",
        answers: ["The University of Edinburgh", "British Columbia University", "Stanford University", "University of Madeira"],
        correctAnswer: "British Columbia University",
        explanation: "Interestingly, Cristiano Ronaldo is also a subject of study at the University of British Columbia Okanagan in Canada. Sociology students at the university have the option to study the life and career of the superstar as a course subject."
    },
    {
        prompt: "How many tattoos does CR7 have?",
        answers: ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
        correctAnswer: "0",
        explanation: "Cristiano Ronaldo has zero tattoos, not even a tiny one! He regularly donates blood and does not want to have to wait months after a tattoo to be able to donate. He is also registered as a bone marrow donor."
    },
    {
        prompt: "Where did Ronaldo first meet with his partner Georgina Rodriguez?",
        answers: ["Real-Madrid training pitch", "Portuguese restaurant", "Gucci Store",  "Holiday in Madeira"],
        correctAnswer: "Gucci Store",
        explanation: "Cristiano met Georgina at the Gucci store in Madrid where she was working as a shop assistant. Georgina was 22 years old and Ronaldo was 31 years old. Ronaldo is said to have asked for Geo's phone number, and their relationship started after meeting in a sports festival 2 days later."
    },
    {
        prompt: "How many hat-tricks has CR7 scored throughout his career?",
        answers: ["35", "44", "57", "63"],
        correctAnswer: "63",
        explanation: "Cristiano Ronaldo has an incredible 63 hat-tricks in his illustrious career with his latest one coming in Saudi Arabia for Al Nassr."
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which one is not a quote from Ronaldo?",
        answers: ["Talent without working hard is nothing.", "It took me 17 years and 114 days to become an overnight success.", "Your limits are defined by your mentality.", "Maybe they hate me because I'm too good."],
        correctAnswer: "It took me 17 years and 114 days to become an overnight success.",
        explanation: "That's a Messi quote ðŸ˜‚"
    },
    {
        prompt: "How many Instagram followers does CR7 have on social media?",
        answers: ["166M followers", "350M followers", "621M followers", "749M followers"],
        correctAnswer: "621M followers",
        explanation: "Cristiano Ronaldo is the most-followed person on Instagram, with over 621 million followers. Messi is the second most followed, with 499 million followers. Messi can compete Ronaldo on the pitch, but off the pitch, CR7 is something else."
    },
]

export default questions